<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-05-08T21:19:14+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">DD-Jekyll Website</title><entry><title type="html">Paint</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/creative/2020/05/08/paint.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Paint" /><published>2020-05-08T09:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-05-08T09:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/creative/2020/05/08/paint</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/creative/2020/05/08/paint.html">&lt;p&gt;i wasn’t sure how this one would turn out. I am not a painter, not the most naturally artistic person in the world. When it comes to art, the best thing I got going for me is probably calligraphy/lettering - even then I’m not exactly good at drawing letters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But never mind! Who says you have to be naturally gifted to paint. Honestly, I thought it would just really fun to just play with colours, splatter some acrylic paint around. So that’s exactly what I did. One thing about this though - art supplies are not exactly cheap. Things do add up: brushes, acrylic paint, canvas.. Luckily, we already had brushes and acrylic paint in the house. No canvas though, so we decided to make do with wood. Wood? Yes. Inspired by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marchemeon.com/&quot;&gt;Marc Hemeon&lt;/a&gt; and his beautiful paintings, I picked up some wood that just happened to be there lying around… and painted on it. And it worked! It had a nice smooth surface, so it was relatively easy to work with. I spent the next hour or so making a complete mess and having lots of fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/ocean.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Smiley face&quot; height=&quot;100%&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know about you, but sometimes painting, drawing, and all these’ artsy’ things can be quite daunting especially if you’re new to it, and you’re not naturally gifted. But I think this is the perfect time to just experiment. The aim is not to impress anyone, it’s just to have fun and have a creative outlet. Some of you might find it helpful, especially during this weird situation where many of us might have a lot of pent-up frustration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So today’s idea isn’t super complicated. Grab some paints, brushes, and some type of flat surface, and paint away!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have fun 😊&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jess</name></author><summary type="html">i wasn’t sure how this one would turn out. I am not a painter, not the most naturally artistic person in the world. When it comes to art, the best thing I got going for me is probably calligraphy/lettering - even then I’m not exactly good at drawing letters.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/paint.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/paint.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Learn to Code</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/education/2020/05/06/learn-to-code.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Learn to Code" /><published>2020-05-06T09:37:11+01:00</published><updated>2020-05-06T09:37:11+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/education/2020/05/06/learn-to-code</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/education/2020/05/06/learn-to-code.html">&lt;p&gt;today’s daily diversion is actually what brought this website to life! I have always been intrigued by coding and the tech world.  It feel very relevant too to the field I’m in, which is (behavioural) design - &lt;em&gt;I sense a post coming on what behavioural design is!&lt;/em&gt; I feel like in the direction that we’re heading in, it seems inevitable that technology will take over pretty much most things in our lives. So I guess instead of resisting it, might as well try to understand it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took my first baby step last year when I decided to buy an online web development course. It was very basic yet very helpful. It gave me the foundation I needed to work with. But as I’m sure you know, the way to learn things is by doing. And unfortunately, I didn’t have any real project to work on. Everything I did was based off instructions given in the lectures, and as a result I wasn’t really able to have a deeper understanding of how things worked. Not that I have a deep understanding of it now 😅, but I suppose I can say that I’m more confident about it now than I was about a year ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then life got busy and I slowly lost all my willpower to continue practicing to code. All kinds of excuses were made. It was easy to say “I’m tired, I have no time”. But now I feel like that doesn’t apply anymore. When you’re locked in the house and not allowed to go out, and all you have is time, I suppose it’s the perfect time to do everything you’ve always wanted to do. So I decided to do just that - give myself a project. Build a website! How? Learn to code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, I know that we have all these amazing platforms like Squarespace, Wix, and Weebly that help us create beautiful websites without having to know the first thing about coding. My &lt;a href=&quot;www.jessmessdesign.com&quot;&gt;Jess’ Mess&lt;/a&gt; website is built on Squarespace. It’s great! But I did want to challenge myself because, after all, I had to find a way to kill time (and not kill myself as a result of boredom).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So here is the end-product! If you wondered why this website was so simple and basic, well.. I guess this answers your question. I &lt;em&gt;had&lt;/em&gt; to make it very basic and simple because I’m a complete novice. But it’s so satisfying to see the site up and running!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re also wanting to learn to code, here are some good sources you might find useful:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.codecademy.com/&quot;&gt;Codeacademy&lt;/a&gt; - they are actually giving away free premium memberships for people who have been directly impacted by the Coronavirus e.g. people on furlough. I did this briefly after I did my first web development course.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.killervideostore.com/&quot;&gt;Stefan Mischook’s online course&lt;/a&gt; - this is the course I did. I enjoyed doing this course, and at the end of every chapter he has a quiz to make sure you understand the concepts.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coursera.org/search?query=coding&amp;amp;&quot;&gt;Coursera&lt;/a&gt; - they also have some free courses on basic coding languages, in partnership with and delivered by top universities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this is something you’ve always wanted to do, why not do it now? These three sources are a great place to start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good luck!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S. Sharing ideas of things to do is fine and all, but do we actually follow through with them? Subscribe to my newsletter now to get updates on my personal experience and (some failed) attempts on actually doing the things I write about - and hear from other people about their experiences ☺️&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jess</name></author><summary type="html">today’s daily diversion is actually what brought this website to life! I have always been intrigued by coding and the tech world. It feel very relevant too to the field I’m in, which is (behavioural) design - I sense a post coming on what behavioural design is! I feel like in the direction that we’re heading in, it seems inevitable that technology will take over pretty much most things in our lives. So I guess instead of resisting it, might as well try to understand it.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/learn-to-code.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/learn-to-code.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Take Pictures</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/life/2020/05/02/take-pictures.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Take Pictures" /><published>2020-05-02T09:37:11+01:00</published><updated>2020-05-02T09:37:11+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/life/2020/05/02/take-pictures</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/life/2020/05/02/take-pictures.html">&lt;p&gt;in the age of selfies and Instagram, and high-resolution cameras on our phones, taking pictures doesn’t sound like an activity we need reminding of. If anything, it feels like sometimes we forget to actually take a second to enjoy where we are, what we’re doing, and who we’re with. But I do wonder if that’s actually due to our obsession of impressing others, rather than a healthy desire to remember moments dear to our hearts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry, I don’t mean to sound all philosophical (and pretentious). I think my point is simply that I often take pictures because I subconsciously think about impressing other people and getting ‘likes’. When really, if I really think about it, the beauty of taking pictures is the act of documenting moments that you’ll want to remember 10, 20, 50 years from now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you read my Write a Journal entry, then you’ll know where I’m going with this. This isn’t the best moment in the history of humankind, but there is definitely a lot to learn from this period. A lot of us, if not all of us, have found ourselves in unfamiliar situations. How we’re adapting to this hasn’t ceased to amaze me. Is this the new normal?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But if we are adaptable creatures, then it probably means when all of this is over, we’ll probably forget the intricate details of our experiences during this lockdown. And if we forget, then how do we share what we learned from this to the future generation? Or, if that sounds too pretentious (again), we can at least use these pictures just to remember our past self, and how we dealt with weird things and uncertainties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been taking more pictures since the lockdown. Silly ones, though. Not highly crafted images. But pictures of me, and the people I’m with, going about our days. Sometimes doing silly things, sometimes just doing normal daily activities. The key, though, is to capture raw moments so in the future, we can have something to look back on, and maybe have a laugh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have fun!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jess</name></author><summary type="html">in the age of selfies and Instagram, and high-resolution cameras on our phones, taking pictures doesn’t sound like an activity we need reminding of. If anything, it feels like sometimes we forget to actually take a second to enjoy where we are, what we’re doing, and who we’re with. But I do wonder if that’s actually due to our obsession of impressing others, rather than a healthy desire to remember moments dear to our hearts.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/take-pictures.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/take-pictures.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Dance</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/fitness/2020/04/30/dance.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dance" /><published>2020-04-30T09:37:11+01:00</published><updated>2020-04-30T09:37:11+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/fitness/2020/04/30/dance</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/fitness/2020/04/30/dance.html">&lt;p&gt;one good thing about being in lockdown is that you can go for a run and dance outside (for a good while) before you see another person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I think about the lockdown too much, my head starts to hurt and freak out about not knowing when all this will end. So I find that it’s best to distract myself by keeping busy and staying active. If you’ve read my second newsletter then you’ll know that I’ve decided to make running a regular thing in my life (if you’re not subscribed and don’t know what I’m talking about, you can read that &lt;a href=&quot;https://mailchi.mp/f8ad3e47f422/newsletter-2-i-went-for-a-run&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. You can sign up for the newsletter below for some reading materials for when you’re bored and have nothing better to do). That’s exactly what I did last Saturday, I went for a run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t say that I enjoyed every single second of that run, but I do have to admit that the post-run feeling was great. I was pretty proud of myself for having completed the first task of the Couch to 5K programme, and maybe it was a combination of that and the warm weather, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/track/47w6S27JF4Zvrz1Wd6R66Z?si=LBy15BVbTh-yQ4fhkYTI5g&quot;&gt;the song I was listening to&lt;/a&gt;, but I kind of felt this weird need to just start dancing around in the middle of nowhere (where nobody could see me, because I still have a sense of pride).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I did. Then I realised how much I’d missed dancing. I used to dance quite a bit when I was younger. It was fun. And then I’m not sure what happened - I guess life took over. But the need to move never left. I think this is why I’m so drawn to yoga - moving your body fluidly sends you into a trance. No thoughts, just movement. It feels so liberating, especially at a time where we’re constantly reminded of the confusing state of the world, which can cause a lot of anxiety. I think what made it more fun, though, is doing it outside. All the space and the sunshine, having an entire road all to yourself, it feels so good. It feels like complete freedom amidst all the restrictions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dancing outside might be a bit of a stretch to a lot of you, but maybe just put on some good music, and dance your heart out in your bedroom. See how that makes you feel 😊&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jess</name></author><summary type="html">one good thing about being in lockdown is that you can go for a run and dance outside (for a good while) before you see another person.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/dance.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/dance.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Write a Journal</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/life/2020/04/28/write-a-journal.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Write a Journal" /><published>2020-04-28T09:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-04-28T09:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/life/2020/04/28/write-a-journal</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/life/2020/04/28/write-a-journal.html">&lt;p&gt;it’s been just over a month now since the government told us to stay at home. I don’t know about you, but I find it quite hard to find the perfect word to describe the sentiment of this situation, and to describe how I feel about it all. It feels like everything happened so suddenly, and escalated so quickly. The whole thing is so unprecedented that I feel I lack the framework to comprehend what’s going on now and what will happen next.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being in lockdown and isolated is not completely new to humankind, I suppose, but how often does it really happen? And how crazy has this year been? I’m not here to talk statistics, I’m just trying to make sense of everything, perhaps like you are too - of how strange everything has been, but how at the same time, we as a species have shown how resilient and adaptable we are. And again, how often does this happen?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frank Chimero wrote &lt;a href=&quot;https://frankchimero.com/blog/2020/today-today-today/&quot;&gt;a nice piece about being in an incubation period&lt;/a&gt; and how “being in the incubator denies you your life for a time but can give back a different perspective”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The days seem to go by really fast, and maybe it’s because I’m trying my best to keep busy and find new things to do (things that I suppose I would not normally do), or maybe it’s because I can’t help but try to create, and settle into a new routine. But this feels like a significant, defining period, and that as much as I hate that this is happening and affecting so many people, it’s also something that I don’t want to forget, because we have so much to learn from this. Just like what Frank said, this is the moment that can give us a different perspective.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So for today’s idea, I propose that we all write a journal. Maybe it doesn’t have to be everyday, but I think it would be nice to record this period of our lives, so we can remember this period, and remember how it made us feel. How it made us more appreciative of the things we used to take for granted, more appreciative of the healthcare workers, and of all the key workers. How it made us remember to check in on our friends and family, to take care of each other, and to connect with each other. Because we adapt, and when things get better and we’re out of lockdown, I’d hate to think that we’d all just revert back to our old ways of living and forget about this new perspective.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So maybe, if we write a journal and record this period of our lives, it can help us be more grateful later?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just a thought :)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jess</name></author><summary type="html">it’s been just over a month now since the government told us to stay at home. I don’t know about you, but I find it quite hard to find the perfect word to describe the sentiment of this situation, and to describe how I feel about it all. It feels like everything happened so suddenly, and escalated so quickly. The whole thing is so unprecedented that I feel I lack the framework to comprehend what’s going on now and what will happen next.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/write-a-journal.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/write-a-journal.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Listen to Podcast</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/entertainment/2020/04/26/listen-to-podcast.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Listen to Podcast" /><published>2020-04-26T09:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-04-26T09:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/entertainment/2020/04/26/listen-to-podcast</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/entertainment/2020/04/26/listen-to-podcast.html">&lt;p&gt;the world of podcasts is wonderful. I’m someone who has always enjoyed listening to the radio. Hearing stories and conversations on the radio has always felt like a treat - getting to know how other people think, talk, and see the world. Not just that though. There’s something about voices that I find just so relaxing and soothing (some more than others, perhaps. My top two favourite voices: &lt;a href=&quot;https://99percentinvisible.org/&quot;&gt;Roman Mars&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&quot;https://onbeing.org/&quot;&gt;Krista Tippett&lt;/a&gt;. You’re welcome).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think most of the time I gravitate towards interview/conversation-type podcasts. It’s always nice to also listen to an interview with someone you don’t know, because you almost always end up learning something new, and you also get to discover new people, with unique interests you might not be exposed to otherwise. It gives you different perspectives, I guess. Then you also have podcasts with narratives and a storytelling feel, that immerse you into someone else’s life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The absence of work commute and travel as a result of the lockdown has kind of reduced my podcast consumption, because this was what I had my ears in during work commute and travels. Now that I’m not doing that anymore, I realise I haven’t been listening to podcasts as much. So for today’s daily diversion idea, I thought this would be a nice one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love finding out new interesting podcasts, so thought you might enjoy a list of interesting podcasts too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For an interview/conversation-style podcast:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tim Ferriss ❤️&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Joe Rogan Experience ❤️&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;On Being&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How I Built This&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Without Fail&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Making Sense with Sam Harris ❤️&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Design Matters ❤️&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Deliciously Ella&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Big Questions with Cal Fussman&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a documentary-style podcast:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Serial (crime)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Start-Up (business)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Heavyweight (documented journeys of people trying to reconnect) ❤️&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a journalistic-type podcast:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Radiolab ❤️&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;99% Invisible&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reply All ❤️&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Planet Money&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Invisibilia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a story-type podcast:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;This American Life&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Death, Sex, and Money&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Snap Judgment&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Truth (fiction stories)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dan Carlin’s Hardcore History (this is a history podcast, brilliantly told in the most engaging narrative).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And for all the Behavioural Science nerds out there, I’ve got extra stuff for you:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Freakonomics ❤️&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Choiceology&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Brainy Business with Melina Palmer&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hidden Brain ❤️&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully there’s something for everyone in that list. It’s quite a long one, so it should keep you busy for a while. And when you’re out of things to do again.. come back for Daily Diversion #8 for another idea #shamelessplug 😉&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jess</name></author><summary type="html">the world of podcasts is wonderful. I’m someone who has always enjoyed listening to the radio. Hearing stories and conversations on the radio has always felt like a treat - getting to know how other people think, talk, and see the world. Not just that though. There’s something about voices that I find just so relaxing and soothing (some more than others, perhaps. My top two favourite voices: Roman Mars &amp;amp; Krista Tippett. You’re welcome).</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/podcast.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/podcast.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Learn to Handstand</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/fitness/2020/04/24/learn-to-handstand.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Learn to Handstand" /><published>2020-04-24T09:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-04-24T09:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/fitness/2020/04/24/learn-to-handstand</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/fitness/2020/04/24/learn-to-handstand.html">&lt;p&gt;there’s something about doing inversions that makes you feel strong. Being able to stand on your head, or your arms, or your hands, kind of makes you feel like you can do anything. The kind of feeling you might gravitate towards during times of uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are plenty of research showing that exercising is good not just for your physical health, but also for your mental health. When we exercise, our body produces endorphins that trigger a positive feeling in the body. No wonder we always feel good after an exercise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What makes it even better though, is that if you stick with it and stay disciplined, you’ll start to see improvements and feel so much stronger. I think this is one of the reasons why I love starting the day with a yoga practice. When you start off the day feeling strong, it just gives you the feeling that you can handle whatever life is going to throw at you that day. Okay maybe not that dramatic, but you know what I mean. You just feel a lot more confident than you would otherwise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that everything feels so uncertain and we don’t really know what is going to happen even in the next few days, I find that focusing on taking back control through physical exercise has been massively helpful. Being on furlough has the effect of making days feel unstructured, so sticking to a routine and giving yourself a project help a lot. So, in the physical fitness department, my project/goal for this lockdown is learn to do a handstand. It’s definitely going to take years to perfect, but I think right now I’d be happy to be able to kick up to a handstand and hold for (at least!) a second.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Practicing Ashtanga yoga has helped a lot in terms of building an upper body strength, but supplementing it with other forms of exercise will accelerate your progress for sure. I’ve been working on arms and shoulders more, and have definitely felt a difference. Core is key too though, something which I haven’t really paid that much attention to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some videos you might find useful:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V5fiBESK_7U&amp;amp;list=WL&amp;amp;index=25&amp;amp;t=1629s&quot;&gt;Kino MacGregor’s Shoulders and arms workout&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q587Mq8VbrM&quot;&gt;School of Calisthenics’ learn to handstand&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5Pgfexjfb20&amp;amp;list=WL&amp;amp;index=24&amp;amp;t=1047s&quot;&gt;Kino MacGregor’s L sit core strength workout&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6X0J51uHxrI&quot;&gt;Gina Scarangella’s handstand tips &amp;amp; drills&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zErb6KNN6HU&quot;&gt;Yoga with Briohny’s handstand basics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good luck!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jess</name></author><summary type="html">there’s something about doing inversions that makes you feel strong. Being able to stand on your head, or your arms, or your hands, kind of makes you feel like you can do anything. The kind of feeling you might gravitate towards during times of uncertainty.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/handstand.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/handstand.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Cook Moroccan</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/food/2020/04/21/cook-moroccan.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cook Moroccan" /><published>2020-04-21T09:37:11+01:00</published><updated>2020-04-21T09:37:11+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/food/2020/04/21/cook-moroccan</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/food/2020/04/21/cook-moroccan.html">&lt;p&gt;the long commute back home from work, rushing off to meet friends to at the pub, trying to fit in time for the gym. This action packed life meant that when we cooked we cooked quickly: a stir fry, a quick pasta dish. And when we did, it often came at a cost: flavour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the hidden benefits of this new slower life, that has been thrust upon us, is that we can now monitor a slowly simmering pot as we exercise in the garden, talk shit over zoom and commute from the living room to the kitchen. There’s no better time than to sketch your culinary legs than with a tender Moroccan beef and apricot stew.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While this might not be a strictly authentic Moroccan Tagine, it’s the flavour that counts and this dish certainly has that in abundance. Plus, who has a Tagine pot lying around?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;tagine&quot; src=&quot;/tagine.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Smiley face&quot; height=&quot;auto&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Serves 4-6&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ingredients:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This recipe is by no means an exact science. Chop and change ingredients depending what is available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Olive oil&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;850g diced beef (lamb also works well)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 red onions, roughly chopped&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;6 garlic gloves, thinly sliced&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 tps ras al hanout (make it yourself from those neglected spices you have at the back of the cupboard, you have the time)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A few splashes of red wine (optional, although hopefully you’ll be sipping this at the time anyway)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 tps of harissa&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3 tps of tomato paste&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 tps of honey&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;4-5 small potatoes, halved&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;600ml of stock&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;4 tbs of red lentils&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Toasted flaked almonds&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Parsley, roughly chopped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Heat olive oil over a high heat in a heavy bottomed pot (a dutch oven works best). In batches brown the beef so as to avoid over crowding and then take the meat and juices out of the pan set aside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add a small amount of oil to the pan, followed by the red onions and garlic. Let the onions cook over until they are translucent. Now you can start layering your flavours. First add the ras al honout (all of those left over spices sitting in your drawer that you promised yourself you’d use one day, this is your chance) and stir. Then add wine, harissa, tomato paste and honey. Return the meat and juices to the pot, followed by the chunks of potato. Cook gently for 1-2 minutes and then pour over the stock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bring the pot to a boil then cover and transfer to a pre-heated oven 160C/140C fan/gas 3 for 2h 30m (if you don’t have a pot that can be put in the oven, leave it on the hob on a low heat for 1h 30m or until the beef is tender). Add the lentils with around 30m to go and the apricots with 15m to go. If you have a slow cooker, you can always use that for added tenderness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Toast almonds on a dry pan for 2-3 minutes until golden. Serve the stew on a bed of couscous topped with almonds, parsley and a dollop of greek yoghurt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stews always benefit from resting in a pot for a day or so, which gives the flavours an opportunity to get to know one and other a little more. So don’t be surprised if tomorrow’s leftovers overshadow today’s main event.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Eoin</name></author><summary type="html">the long commute back home from work, rushing off to meet friends to at the pub, trying to fit in time for the gym. This action packed life meant that when we cooked we cooked quickly: a stir fry, a quick pasta dish. And when we did, it often came at a cost: flavour.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/cook-moroccan.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/cook-moroccan.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Watch a Crime Documentary</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/entertainment/2020/04/20/watch-a-crime-doc.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Watch a Crime Documentary" /><published>2020-04-20T09:37:11+01:00</published><updated>2020-04-20T09:37:11+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/entertainment/2020/04/20/watch-a-crime-doc</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/entertainment/2020/04/20/watch-a-crime-doc.html">&lt;p&gt;this might not be the most productive thing to do during a lockdown, but this is not a productivity contest. And documentaries always feel more.. educational if that makes anyone feel any better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a special place in my heart for crime documentaries. One of the first crime series I got addicted to (like millions of others. Literally, millions of people loved it so much that it was the single most downloaded podcast ever made) was [Serial]. This podcast followed the story of a guy who was convicted guilty of the murder of his ex girlfriend and investigated his innocence. Then came Making a Murderer. This was such a compelling story that I just could not stop watching it. I think I finished it in two days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now Netflix is killing it with all their original crime documentary series. The most recent one I watched is Tiger King and… I loved it (maybe for all the wrong reasons). With seven episodes and new characters introduced in almost every episode, this series just keeps you wondering what’s going to happen next, and also asking yourself “did this actually happen? Why is this &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt; weird?”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that we’re in lockdown (and it seems like all I have is time), I asked Phoebe to give me some recommendations of things to watch, and she put together &lt;strong&gt;this amazing list of must-watch crime documentaries&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Jinx&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Unabomber: in his own words&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Evil Genius&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tell Me Who I Am&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Three Identical Strangers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Making a Murderer&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Keepers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Trials of Gabriel Fernandez&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Amanda Knox&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Disappearance of Madeleine McCann&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Surviving R Kelly&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tiger King&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Any Louis Theroux Documentaries&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Abducted in Plain Sight&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Don’t Fuck with Cats&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Voyeur&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Icarus&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Leaving Neverland&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fyre Festival&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bowling for Columbine&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Mind of Aaron Hernandez&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Devil Next Door&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Confession Killer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bringing you quality content, thanks to Phoebe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jess</name></author><summary type="html">this might not be the most productive thing to do during a lockdown, but this is not a productivity contest. And documentaries always feel more.. educational if that makes anyone feel any better.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/crime-doc.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/crime-doc.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Lettering</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/creative/2020/04/18/lettering.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lettering" /><published>2020-04-18T09:37:11+01:00</published><updated>2020-04-18T09:37:11+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/creative/2020/04/18/lettering</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/creative/2020/04/18/lettering.html">&lt;p&gt;some people are born creative. Naturally artsy. Others.. not so much. Growing up I always liked the idea of doing art, but just never had the talent to do that. But I thought drawing letters were fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s something about beautiful lettering and calligraphy that just feels so satisfying and makes me happy. Because I’ve never been technical about it (because I lack the skills to do so), I thought that doing an online lettering class would be a great way to change that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve done a couple of Skillshare classes before on calligraphy and lettering, but it’s been a while and I feel like it’s one of those things where if you don’t practice regularly, you start to forget and become rusty. So now that I’m on furlough… it feels like the perfect time to take online lettering and calligraphy classes again!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Skillshare is a paid service, but like everyone else at this time, they are offering a free trial (so people like us can milk these services as much as we can).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So here are the two classes I’m doing:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seb Lester’s Calligraphy Course&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jessica Hische’s Drop Cap Course&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will assure you that I won’t be able to finish these classes in a day, but that’s good - staying busy is what we want at this time!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jess</name></author><summary type="html">some people are born creative. Naturally artsy. Others.. not so much. Growing up I always liked the idea of doing art, but just never had the talent to do that. But I thought drawing letters were fun.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/lettering.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/lettering.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>