<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-04-27T10:21:42+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">DD-Jekyll Website</title><entry><title type="html">Listen to Podcast</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/entertainment/2020/04/26/listen-to-podcast.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Listen to Podcast" /><published>2020-04-26T09:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-04-26T09:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/entertainment/2020/04/26/listen-to-podcast</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/entertainment/2020/04/26/listen-to-podcast.html">&lt;p&gt;the world of podcasts is wonderful. I’m someone who has always enjoyed listening to the radio. Hearing stories and conversations on the radio has always felt like a treat - getting to know how other people think, talk, and see the world. Not just that though. There’s something about voices that I find just so relaxing and soothing (some more than others, perhaps. My top two favourite voices: &lt;a href=&quot;https://99percentinvisible.org/&quot;&gt;Roman Mars&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&quot;https://onbeing.org/&quot;&gt;Krista Tippett&lt;/a&gt;. You’re welcome).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think most of the time I gravitate towards interview/conversation-type podcasts. It’s always nice to also listen to an interview with someone you don’t know, because you almost always end up learning something new, and you also get to discover new people, with unique interests you might not be exposed to otherwise. It gives you different perspectives, I guess. Then you also have podcasts with narratives and a storytelling feel, that immerse you into someone else’s life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The absence of work commute and travel as a result of the lockdown has kind of reduced my podcast consumption, because this was what I had my ears in during work commute and travels. Now that I’m not doing that anymore, I realise I haven’t been listening to podcasts as much. So for today’s daily diversion idea, I thought this would be a nice one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love finding out new interesting podcasts, so thought you might enjoy a list of interesting podcasts too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For an interview/conversation-style podcast:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tim Ferriss ❤️&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Joe Rogan Experience ❤️&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;On Being&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How I Built This&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Without Fail&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Making Sense with Sam Harris ❤️&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Design Matters ❤️&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Deliciously Ella&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Big Questions with Cal Fussman&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a documentary-style podcast:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Serial (crime)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Start-Up (business)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Heavyweight (documented journeys of people trying to reconnect) ❤️&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a journalistic-type podcast:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Radiolab ❤️&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;99% Invisible&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reply All ❤️&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Planet Money&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Invisibilia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a story-type podcast:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;This American Life&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Death, Sex, and Money&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Snap Judgment&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Truth (fiction stories)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dan Carlin’s Hardcore History (this is a history podcast, brilliantly told in the most engaging narrative).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And for all the Behavioural Science nerds out there, I’ve got extra stuff for you:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Freakonomics ❤️&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Choiceology&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Brainy Business with Melina Palmer&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hidden Brain ❤️&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully there’s something for everyone in that list. It’s quite a long one, so it should keep you busy for a while. And when you’re out of things to do again.. come back for Daily Diversion #8 for another idea #shamelessplug 😉&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jess</name></author><summary type="html">the world of podcasts is wonderful. I’m someone who has always enjoyed listening to the radio. Hearing stories and conversations on the radio has always felt like a treat - getting to know how other people think, talk, and see the world. Not just that though. There’s something about voices that I find just so relaxing and soothing (some more than others, perhaps. My top two favourite voices: Roman Mars &amp;amp; Krista Tippett. You’re welcome).</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/podcast.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/podcast.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Learn to Handstand</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/fitness/2020/04/24/learn-to-handstand.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Learn to Handstand" /><published>2020-04-24T09:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-04-24T09:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/fitness/2020/04/24/learn-to-handstand</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/fitness/2020/04/24/learn-to-handstand.html">&lt;p&gt;there’s something about doing inversions that makes you feel strong. Being able to stand on your head, or your arms, or your hands, kind of makes you feel like you can do anything. The kind of feeling you might gravitate towards during times of uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are plenty of research showing that exercising is good not just for your physical health, but also for your mental health. When we exercise, our body produces endorphins that trigger a positive feeling in the body. No wonder we always feel good after an exercise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What makes it even better though, is that if you stick with it and stay disciplined, you’ll start to see improvements and feel so much stronger. I think this is one of the reasons why I love starting the day with a yoga practice. When you start off the day feeling strong, it just gives you the feeling that you can handle whatever life is going to throw at you that day. Okay maybe not that dramatic, but you know what I mean. You just feel a lot more confident than you would otherwise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that everything feels so uncertain and we don’t really know what is going to happen even in the next few days, I find that focusing on taking back control through physical exercise has been massively helpful. Being on furlough has the effect of making days feel unstructured, so sticking to a routine and giving yourself a project help a lot. So, in the physical fitness department, my project/goal for this lockdown is learn to do a handstand. It’s definitely going to take years to perfect, but I think right now I’d be happy to be able to kick up to a handstand and hold for (at least!) a second.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Practicing Ashtanga yoga has helped a lot in terms of building an upper body strength, but supplementing it with other forms of exercise will accelerate your progress for sure. I’ve been working on arms and shoulders more, and have definitely felt a difference. Core is key too though, something which I haven’t really paid that much attention to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some videos you might find useful:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V5fiBESK_7U&amp;amp;list=WL&amp;amp;index=25&amp;amp;t=1629s&quot;&gt;Kino MacGregor’s Shoulders and arms workout&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q587Mq8VbrM&quot;&gt;School of Calisthenics’ learn to handstand&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5Pgfexjfb20&amp;amp;list=WL&amp;amp;index=24&amp;amp;t=1047s&quot;&gt;Kino MacGregor’s L sit core strength workout&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6X0J51uHxrI&quot;&gt;Gina Scarangella’s handstand tips &amp;amp; drills&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zErb6KNN6HU&quot;&gt;Yoga with Briohny’s handstand basics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good luck!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jess</name></author><summary type="html">there’s something about doing inversions that makes you feel strong. Being able to stand on your head, or your arms, or your hands, kind of makes you feel like you can do anything. The kind of feeling you might gravitate towards during times of uncertainty.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/handstand.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/handstand.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Cook Moroccan</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/food/2020/04/21/cook-moroccan.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cook Moroccan" /><published>2020-04-21T09:37:11+01:00</published><updated>2020-04-21T09:37:11+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/food/2020/04/21/cook-moroccan</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/food/2020/04/21/cook-moroccan.html">&lt;p&gt;the long commute back home from work, rushing off to meet friends to at the pub, trying to fit in time for the gym. This action packed life meant that when we cooked we cooked quickly: a stir fry, a quick pasta dish. And when we did, it often came at a cost: flavour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the hidden benefits of this new slower life, that has been thrust upon us, is that we can now monitor a slowly simmering pot as we exercise in the garden, talk shit over zoom and commute from the living room to the kitchen. There’s no better time than to sketch your culinary legs than with a tender Moroccan beef and apricot stew.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While this might not be a strictly authentic Moroccan Tagine, it’s the flavour that counts and this dish certainly has that in abundance. Plus, who has a Tagine pot lying around?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;tagine&quot; src=&quot;/tagine.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Smiley face&quot; height=&quot;auto&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Serves 4-6&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ingredients:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This recipe is by no means an exact science. Chop and change ingredients depending what is available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Olive oil&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;850g diced beef (lamb also works well)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 red onions, roughly chopped&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;6 garlic gloves, thinly sliced&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 tps ras al hanout (make it yourself from those neglected spices you have at the back of the cupboard, you have the time)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A few splashes of red wine (optional, although hopefully you’ll be sipping this at the time anyway)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 tps of harissa&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3 tps of tomato paste&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 tps of honey&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;4-5 small potatoes, halved&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;600ml of stock&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;4 tbs of red lentils&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Toasted flaked almonds&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Parsley, roughly chopped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Heat olive oil over a high heat in a heavy bottomed pot (a dutch oven works best). In batches brown the beef so as to avoid over crowding and then take the meat and juices out of the pan set aside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add a small amount of oil to the pan, followed by the red onions and garlic. Let the onions cook over until they are translucent. Now you can start layering your flavours. First add the ras al honout (all of those left over spices sitting in your drawer that you promised yourself you’d use one day, this is your chance) and stir. Then add wine, harissa, tomato paste and honey. Return the meat and juices to the pot, followed by the chunks of potato. Cook gently for 1-2 minutes and then pour over the stock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bring the pot to a boil then cover and transfer to a pre-heated oven 160C/140C fan/gas 3 for 2h 30m (if you don’t have a pot that can be put in the oven, leave it on the hob on a low heat for 1h 30m or until the beef is tender). Add the lentils with around 30m to go and the apricots with 15m to go. If you have a slow cooker, you can always use that for added tenderness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Toast almonds on a dry pan for 2-3 minutes until golden. Serve the stew on a bed of couscous topped with almonds, parsley and a dollop of greek yoghurt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stews always benefit from resting in a pot for a day or so, which gives the flavours an opportunity to get to know one and other a little more. So don’t be surprised if tomorrow’s leftovers overshadow today’s main event.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Eoin</name></author><summary type="html">the long commute back home from work, rushing off to meet friends to at the pub, trying to fit in time for the gym. This action packed life meant that when we cooked we cooked quickly: a stir fry, a quick pasta dish. And when we did, it often came at a cost: flavour.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/cook-moroccan.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/cook-moroccan.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Watch a Crime Documentary</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/entertainment/2020/04/20/watch-a-crime-doc.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Watch a Crime Documentary" /><published>2020-04-20T09:37:11+01:00</published><updated>2020-04-20T09:37:11+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/entertainment/2020/04/20/watch-a-crime-doc</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/entertainment/2020/04/20/watch-a-crime-doc.html">&lt;p&gt;this might not be the most productive thing to do during a lockdown, but this is not a productivity contest. And documentaries always feel more.. educational if that makes anyone feel any better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a special place in my heart for crime documentaries. One of the first crime series I got addicted to (like millions of others. Literally, millions of people loved it so much that it was the single most downloaded podcast ever made) was [Serial]. This podcast followed the story of a guy who was convicted guilty of the murder of his ex girlfriend and investigated his innocence. Then came Making a Murderer. This was such a compelling story that I just could not stop watching it. I think I finished it in two days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now Netflix is killing it with all their original crime documentary series. The most recent one I watched is Tiger King and… I loved it (maybe for all the wrong reasons). With seven episodes and new characters introduced in almost every episode, this series just keeps you wondering what’s going to happen next, and also asking yourself “did this actually happen? Why is this &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt; weird?”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that we’re in lockdown (and it seems like all I have is time), I asked Phoebe to give me some recommendations of things to watch, and she put together &lt;strong&gt;this amazing list of must-watch crime documentaries&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Jinx&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Unabomber: in his own words&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Evil Genius&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tell Me Who I Am&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Three Identical Strangers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Making a Murderer&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Keepers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Trials of Gabriel Fernandez&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Amanda Knox&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Disappearance of Madeleine McCann&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Surviving R Kelly&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tiger King&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Any Louis Theroux Documentaries&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Abducted in Plain Sight&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Don’t Fuck with Cats&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Voyeur&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Icarus&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Leaving Neverland&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fyre Festival&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bowling for Columbine&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Mind of Aaron Hernandez&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Devil Next Door&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Confession Killer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bringing you quality content, thanks to Phoebe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jess</name></author><summary type="html">this might not be the most productive thing to do during a lockdown, but this is not a productivity contest. And documentaries always feel more.. educational if that makes anyone feel any better.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/crime-doc.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/crime-doc.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Lettering</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/creative/2020/04/18/lettering.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lettering" /><published>2020-04-18T09:37:11+01:00</published><updated>2020-04-18T09:37:11+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/creative/2020/04/18/lettering</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/creative/2020/04/18/lettering.html">&lt;p&gt;some people are born creative. Naturally artsy. Others.. not so much. Growing up I always liked the idea of doing art, but just never had the talent to do that. But I thought drawing letters were fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s something about beautiful lettering and calligraphy that just feels so satisfying and makes me happy. Because I’ve never been technical about it (because I lack the skills to do so), I thought that doing an online lettering class would be a great way to change that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve done a couple of Skillshare classes before on calligraphy and lettering, but it’s been a while and I feel like it’s one of those things where if you don’t practice regularly, you start to forget and become rusty. So now that I’m on furlough… it feels like the perfect time to take online lettering and calligraphy classes again!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Skillshare is a paid service, but like everyone else at this time, they are offering a free trial (so people like us can milk these services as much as we can).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So here are the two classes I’m doing:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seb Lester’s Calligraphy Course&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jessica Hische’s Drop Cap Course&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will assure you that I won’t be able to finish these classes in a day, but that’s good - staying busy is what we want at this time!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jess</name></author><summary type="html">some people are born creative. Naturally artsy. Others.. not so much. Growing up I always liked the idea of doing art, but just never had the talent to do that. But I thought drawing letters were fun.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/lettering.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/lettering.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Do Yoga</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/fitness/2020/04/16/do-yoga.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Do Yoga" /><published>2020-04-16T09:37:11+01:00</published><updated>2020-04-16T09:37:11+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/fitness/2020/04/16/do-yoga</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/fitness/2020/04/16/do-yoga.html">&lt;p&gt;Yoga has been one of the things that keeps me sane over the past couple of years. And now, it has become an even more important than ever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not being able to go out and to move can also start to feel very debilitating. Going to my yoga studio in the morning before work was something I always looked forward to - not to say it was easy to get out of bed early every morning.. but you definitely forgot about that once you were there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m &lt;em&gt;definitely&lt;/em&gt; not the most athletic person, but yoga made me stronger. And being able to move just feels so liberating. So number two on the list is: &lt;strong&gt;do yoga&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A recent study by Delaney and colleagues (2020) showed that people who make time to exercise regularly during the lockdown get a lot more enjoyment and benefits than those who don’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are plenty of resources out there. If you type in ‘yoga tutorial’ on YouTube, I’m sure you know that thousands of videos will pop up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are my top 3 recommendations:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://stillpointyogalondon.com&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stillpoint Yoga London&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
This is my regular yoga studio, and they are now doing online classes! It’s a Mysore style yoga, but the online classes they’re doing now are all led, so even if you’re a complete beginner and don’t know anything about Ashtanga, you’re in good hands. It’s a paid class, but I really can’t rave about Scott and the community enough - my happy place :)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;hhttps://www.youtube.com/user/KinoYoga&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kino MacGregor YouTube channel&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
To say that Kino is an experienced teacher and practitioner is an understatement. I’m pretty sure she’s been practicing for over 20 years, and her videos range from beginner level to advanced. Her strength building videos are definitely some of my favourites, though they always make me hate her a little while doing them :p&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/yogawithadriene&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yoga with Adriene&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
A classic. This channel was probably one of the first videos I watched years ago when I first started to do yoga. She’s got lots of content, and her 30 days of yoga series are amazing. A great place to start practicing regularly.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully this will inspire you to move your body :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--
You can use HTML elements in Markdown, such as the comment element, and they won't
be affected by a markdown parser. However, if you create an HTML element in your
markdown file, you cannot use markdown syntax within that element's contents.
--&gt;</content><author><name>Jess</name></author><summary type="html">Yoga has been one of the things that keeps me sane over the past couple of years. And now, it has become an even more important than ever.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/do-yoga.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/do-yoga.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Bake a Cake</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/food/2020/04/13/bake-a-cake.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bake a Cake" /><published>2020-04-13T15:37:11+01:00</published><updated>2020-04-13T15:37:11+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/food/2020/04/13/bake-a-cake</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/food/2020/04/13/bake-a-cake.html">&lt;p&gt;when in doubt…bake a cake.
(Not in excess, because we don’t like it when people stockpile and buy too much stuff).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s bake a carrot cake! And let’s also make this very clear - I did not come up with the recipe myself. I am, at best, a mediocre baker. If you’re like me (i.e. bored, wanting to find things to do and experiment a little bit because you’re bored), then this might be fun! The original recipe can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.easypeasyfoodie.com/super-simple-carrot-cake/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the things you need:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cake:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;350g self-raising flour&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;325g dark soft brown sugar&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 tsp cinnamon&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;250g carrots&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;75g walnuts&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;4 medium eggs&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;200ml olive oil&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;4 tbs milk&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frosting:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;180g full fat cream cheese&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;30g icing sugar&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;25g walnuts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s what you need to do:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Preheat the oven to 160C. Grease and line the bottom and sides of a 22cm round cake tin with a double layer of greaseproof paper.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mix together the flour, sugar, cinnamon, roughly chopped walnuts and grated carrots in a large bowl.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Beat together the eggs, olive oil and milk in a large jug.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pour the wet ingredients into the dry ingredients slowly, stirring to make sure all the flour is incorporated.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tip the cake mixture into the lined cake tin and cook for 1h15, or until a skewer (or a fork) comes out clean.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
For the (optional) frosting, simply:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mix the cream cheese and icing sugar together and spread it on the top of the cake. Sprinkle the finely chopped walnuts on the top.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--
You can use HTML elements in Markdown, such as the comment element, and they won't
be affected by a markdown parser. However, if you create an HTML element in your
markdown file, you cannot use markdown syntax within that element's contents.
--&gt;</content><author><name>Jess</name></author><summary type="html">when in doubt…bake a cake. (Not in excess, because we don’t like it when people stockpile and buy too much stuff).</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/BakeaCake.gif" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/BakeaCake.gif" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>