<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-06-08T13:37:34+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">DD-Jekyll Website</title><entry><title type="html">Make a Thank You Card</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/life/2020/06/08/make-a-thank-you-card.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Make a Thank You Card" /><published>2020-06-08T09:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-06-08T09:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/life/2020/06/08/make-a-thank-you-card</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/life/2020/06/08/make-a-thank-you-card.html">&lt;p&gt;i think by now we all have come to realise how important human connection is. This whole not being able to see friends and family really expresses ‘you don’t appreciate what you have until you lose it’ perfectly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s also really interesting to see how lockdown has also strengthened some friendships and relationships - it feels like we are now making more of a deliberate effort to connect with each other and to check in on each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thinking about it from that perspective kind of warms my heart a little bit (as warm as it can be right now - the hanger is really kicking in). Yesterday during a meeting we were asked who made us happy during lockdown, which I thought was a very nice sentiment. And that gave me an idea - wouldn’t it be nice to actually express that thank you to the people who have made our lives happier and easier during lockdown?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I need to start doing this more. Often I just think these things and don’t actually end up doing them. When I was asked that question, I immediately thought about my parents who have been sending selfies and videos (one of which was a video of my dad shaving his head. Lol). I really should get better at replying texts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So today’s idea: make a thank you card! Honestly, it doesn’t even have to be fancy for whoever’s getting it to appreciate it. As they say, it’s the thought that counts (though it also doesn’t mean that you shouldn’t make an effort. Sorry, double negatives. It means that you still should make an effort if possible 😊).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One last thing before I go - thank you dear reader! Whoever you are, wherever you are. Thanks for reading my disorganised thoughts, my (often un-)structured mess 😊&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jess</name></author><summary type="html">i think by now we all have come to realise how important human connection is. This whole not being able to see friends and family really expresses ‘you don’t appreciate what you have until you lose it’ perfectly.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/thank-you.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/thank-you.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Eoin - episode 3</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/journal/2020/06/07/eoin-episode-3.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Eoin - episode 3" /><published>2020-06-07T09:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-06-07T09:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/journal/2020/06/07/eoin-episode-3</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/journal/2020/06/07/eoin-episode-3.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;what did you do today?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Finished one book and started another. The one I put down was Michael Pollan’s ‘How to change your mind’ - a deep dive into the often misunderstood world of psychedelics. Pollan is an immersive journalist, type of writer who while writing a book about architecture builds his own house and when writing a book about food lives with his own cows for a year. You can probably imagine what he does in preparation for his latest book. The latter chapters about psychedelic treatment to addiction and depression are particularly interesting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The book I picked up is ‘Dark lies the island’ by Irish writer Kevin Barry. The back of the book promises me a collection of short stories about: disco at the end of the world, a teenage goth on a terror mission, scouse real-ale enthusiasts, and occult weirdness in the woods. I’m only one story one but so good so far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did you think about something or someone you hadn’t in a while?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
A friend of mine who I haven’t seen in years. They would always announce (refreshingly) how much they didn’t know. That they were by no means an expert in anything. That they’d struggle to even pick a ‘mastermind topic’. Wise words, especially in a time when we are suddenly experts in epidemiology, the economy, and behavioural fatigue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did you have a meaningful interaction with someone (or was it just meaningless zoom faff)?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I’ve been Netflix partying (watching films with friends online), which usually ends up being a chaotic yet fun mess. Meaningful? Probably not but I wouldn’t say completely meaningless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did anything interesting happen?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The sun in Ireland continued to shine. This amount of good weather is highly abnormal. More suspicious than anything else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did you learn something new about yourself?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I find I don’t miss the pub as much as I thought I would. There seems little point to getting pissed over zoom. This feels like the easiest time I’ll ever have to not drink in excess - so therefore I haven’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do you feel about lockdown today?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I feel future-oriented. It’s a nice form of present-escapism. People have started to talk about after - what they’ll do when everything finally settles down. And I don’t blame them - it seems like an eternity. It feels so long ago that the virus was a small afterthought of a news item, hidden away behind articles on Brexit, the US election and the Premier League. It feels a long time ago that I casually dismissed the outbreak in China with “well, that would never happen here”. Now I’ve allowed my mind to wander back to a covid-free world. Planning future holidays in my head being the funnest of these mental activities - a 5 day road-trip around the Scottish Highlands? Yes please!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Eoin</name></author><summary type="html">what did you do today? Finished one book and started another. The one I put down was Michael Pollan’s ‘How to change your mind’ - a deep dive into the often misunderstood world of psychedelics. Pollan is an immersive journalist, type of writer who while writing a book about architecture builds his own house and when writing a book about food lives with his own cows for a year. You can probably imagine what he does in preparation for his latest book. The latter chapters about psychedelic treatment to addiction and depression are particularly interesting.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/eoin-lockdown.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/eoin-lockdown.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Make Your Own Pickles</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/food/2020/06/07/pickles.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Make Your Own Pickles" /><published>2020-06-07T09:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-06-07T09:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/food/2020/06/07/pickles</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/food/2020/06/07/pickles.html">&lt;p&gt;during lockdown I have jumped on the pickling and fermenting bandwagon. Fermenting, in particular, has become very fashionable in recent times aided somewhat by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.co.uk/Noma-Guide-Fermentation-Foundations-Flavor/dp/1579657184&quot;&gt;Noma&lt;/a&gt; becoming a trendy thing to namedrop in conversation. Many people use the terms, pickling and fermenting, interchangeably yet there is a difference. Pickling involves putting food into an acidic brine to produce a sour flavour, while fermenting gives flavour without any added acid. Ferments have some serious health benefits. They are loaded with probiotics and can improve digestion. Pickles, on the other hand, aren’t the healthiest of options. It doesn’t stop them being delicious however.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before getting started it’s important to properly sterilise the jars you’ll be using. Do this by washing thoroughly with soapy water and then putting them in an oven on low heat for 10 mins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sky is the limit when it comes to pickling and fermenting, but here are a few recipes on the easy side to get you going…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simple Fermented Cucumbers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The simplest recipes are often the best. For fermenting to take place &lt;strong&gt;all you need is water, salt, vegetables and time!&lt;/strong&gt; From this foundation, you can experiment by adding garlic, herbs or whole spices. This fermentation recipe also works well with carrots and radish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How to make:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To make the brine, combine warm water and 2 tablespoons of sea salt. Set aside to cool.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cut the cucumbers into chunks and tightly pack into your sterilised jar alongside smashed garlic cloves and fresh dill.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pour over the brine, ensuring that the vegetables are completely covered.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Screw on the lid and then leave to ferment for 10-14 days. Try to store the jar somewhere that doesn’t fluctuate in temperature, so don’t leave it in direct sunlight or near the oven.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Serving suggestion:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fermented cucumbers are the ideal companion to cold meats in a sandwich.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chinese-Style Smashed Cucumber&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you can’t wait 14 days then try these quick refrigerator pickles. These are vegetables pickled in a vinegar, water, and salt (sometimes sugar, as well) and then stored in the fridge for a few days. Quick pickles don’t quite give you the intense flavour that fermented pickles do. So for this recipe I’ve compensated by using ingredients that really pack a punch - soy sauce and chilli.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What you’ll need:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cucumbers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Salt&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Soy sauce&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rice vinegar&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1/2 tablespoon Sugar&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dried chillis (chilli flakes work well too)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Whole black peppercorns&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sesame oil&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Garlic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How to make:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Use a rolling pin, or the flat surface of a large knife to smash a whole cucumber slightly. Then roughly chop into chunks.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Place the cucumbers into a bowl and sprinkle salt on top. Set aside in the fridge for an hour.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Over a low heat dissolve the sugar with equal parts soy sauce, water, rice vinegar.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add in the rest of the ingredients and leave to cool.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Take the cucumbers out of the fridge and strain out the excess water, then pack them into a jar. Pour the mixture over and refrigerate overnight.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Serving suggestion:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perfect addition to a rice bowl.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_-JLeZbixM4&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fermented Mushrooms&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This one is adapted from a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_-JLeZbixM4&quot;&gt;Brad Leone Recipe&lt;/a&gt; (something of a god amongst youtube fermenters). It’s definitely one for the more experimental minded as the texture of mushrooms isn’t to everyone’s liking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What you’ll need:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mushrooms (splash out for shiitake, it’s worth it)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mirin&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Light Soy Sauce&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ginger (optional)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Seaweed (use a tough seaweed such as Kombu) (optional)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How to make:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pack shiitake mushrooms into a jar with chunks of fresh ginger and then top with Mirin seasoning and light soy sauce.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Leave for at room temperature for 7 days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Serving suggestion:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On toasted rye bread with gouda cheese.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pickled Rhubarb&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, one for a sweater tooth. I know rhubarb isn’t the first thing that springs to mind when thinking about what pickling, but trust me, it’s amazing!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;200ml apple cider vinegar&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;100ml water&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3 tablespoons sugar&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;½ tablespoon sea salt&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fresh rhubarb, cut into pieces&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fresh ginger&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cinnamon stick&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cloves&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How to make:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;On a low heat, gently simmer the all the ingredients until the sugar and salt have dissolved.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pour the mixture over a packed jar of chopped rhubarb and seal with the lid.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Refrigerate for 3 days before digging in.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Serving suggestion:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On vanilla ice cream&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Eoin</name></author><summary type="html">during lockdown I have jumped on the pickling and fermenting bandwagon. Fermenting, in particular, has become very fashionable in recent times aided somewhat by Noma becoming a trendy thing to namedrop in conversation. Many people use the terms, pickling and fermenting, interchangeably yet there is a difference. Pickling involves putting food into an acidic brine to produce a sour flavour, while fermenting gives flavour without any added acid. Ferments have some serious health benefits. They are loaded with probiotics and can improve digestion. Pickles, on the other hand, aren’t the healthiest of options. It doesn’t stop them being delicious however.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/pickles.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/pickles.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Cathy - episode 3</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/journal/2020/06/05/cathy-episode-4.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cathy - episode 3" /><published>2020-06-05T09:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-06-05T09:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/journal/2020/06/05/cathy-episode-4</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/journal/2020/06/05/cathy-episode-4.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;what did you do today?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I started my day off with a run, did some meditation, had to do some work, did my laundry, cleaned up the flat and that’s pretty much it for now! I think I’ve been more productive than I ever have in my life because of lockdown so I’m feeling pretty good about things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did you think about something or someone you hadn’t in a while?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Not really, just focusing on the present :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did you have a meaningful interaction with someone (or was it just meaningless zoom faff)?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Nope!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did anything interesting happen?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Nothing out of the ordinary, just a normal day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did you learn something new about yourself?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I think I’m less scared of spiders now after having sucked up two spiders using a vacuum during lockdown so far. I hope they don’t crawl back out haha.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do you feel about lockdown today?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Honestly I feel pretty good about lockdown right now. I found it quite difficult at the beginning and really let myself go. But once I started attending these daily meditation sessions hosted by my friend Ique, I feel it’s really influenced my life in a positive way, where I’m slowly doing things to make my life better - like just this week I’ve started running after having not exercised in years and it feels really good :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the past I’ve always characterised myself as lazy in an ironic way. Like I would always joke about how exercise isn’t really for me, that waking up early wasn’t really my thing, etc. I think in a way I used humour as a way to justify or to deflect the negative parts of being lazy. But I think lockdown has really exacerbated those habits and made me realise the not so funny bits that come with being lazy. Physically, I felt that I had gained a lot of weight and felt quite weak and tired during the day, and mentally it made me feel really negatively towards myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Attending these daily meditations has slowly changed my life habits. Directly, I feel less anxious and stressful, I feel that I’m able to focus more on the present. Indirectly, I think it’s really influenced me to change small things in my life or to try new things which have impacted my life in a positive way, like being open to exercising! Hopefully it’s something I can keep up :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Additional comments?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I think that’s all, thanks for coming to my TED talk haha.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Cathy</name></author><summary type="html">what did you do today? I started my day off with a run, did some meditation, had to do some work, did my laundry, cleaned up the flat and that’s pretty much it for now! I think I’ve been more productive than I ever have in my life because of lockdown so I’m feeling pretty good about things.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/cathy-lockdown.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/cathy-lockdown.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">DIY Coconut Sorbet</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/food/2020/06/02/coconut-sorbet.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="DIY Coconut Sorbet" /><published>2020-06-02T09:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-06-02T09:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/food/2020/06/02/coconut-sorbet</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/food/2020/06/02/coconut-sorbet.html">&lt;p&gt;ever wanted to make your own ice cream? I certainly have, but have always been daunted by expensive churning machines or complicated recipes. This sorbet recipe provides a simple and unique tasting alternative. You won’t have tasted anything like it before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the best things about it is that it’s the perfect pantry recipe, containing only a handful of ingredients (that you may already have).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s what you’ll need:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 cans of coconut milk&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;400ml of honey&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Limes&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sea Salt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How to make:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Using a blender or food processor, give the coconut milk and honey a quick whiz.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mix in sea salt and the juice of one lime. Pour into a plastic tub and put in the freezer.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Every hour or so take a fork and give the sorbet a good mix, scraping through any ice crystals that form. It’s best to do this over the course of 3-4 hours and then leave overnight until solid.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Garnish as much lime zest and sea salt as you like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s really that simple.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Eoin</name></author><summary type="html">ever wanted to make your own ice cream? I certainly have, but have always been daunted by expensive churning machines or complicated recipes. This sorbet recipe provides a simple and unique tasting alternative. You won’t have tasted anything like it before.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/sorbet.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/sorbet.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Make a Cold Brew Coffee</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/food/2020/06/01/cold-brew.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Make a Cold Brew Coffee" /><published>2020-06-01T09:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-06-01T09:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/food/2020/06/01/cold-brew</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/food/2020/06/01/cold-brew.html">&lt;p&gt;this one is one of those nice little pick me ups that is surprisingly really easy to make. Now I think it’s important to preface this by saying that I do drink a lot of coffee, but I am an absolute noob when it comes to coffee jargons and different flavours and finishes and textures and all that fancy stuff that coffee snobs love :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s getting warm here in the UK (though I realise saying it out loud might jinx it), and as I continue to require my daily dose of caffeine, the thought of a cold brew just sounded ideal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the quest for the best cold brew recipe began!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…and it only took about 5 minutes until we found the easiest recipe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ready?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go to your kitchen now and mix 2/3 cup of coffee beans, which makes about 3/4 cup of coarsely-ground coffee, with about 6 cups of water, or about the size of a big mason jar. Give it a bit of a shake, and put it in the fridge. Leave it overnight, or longer for a stronger flavour, and voila! You’ve made yourself a nice cold brew.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Important note: before you serve it, make sure to plunge it in a cafetiere first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Honestly, it tastes so delicious and makes you think why would I pay £5 a cup for this if I can make it at home (because you’re lazy maybe Jess, and can’t always be bothered).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But it’s lockdown season and we gotta keep ourselves entertained right? Give this a try and let me know what you think!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jess</name></author><summary type="html">this one is one of those nice little pick me ups that is surprisingly really easy to make. Now I think it’s important to preface this by saying that I do drink a lot of coffee, but I am an absolute noob when it comes to coffee jargons and different flavours and finishes and textures and all that fancy stuff that coffee snobs love :)</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/cold-brew.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/cold-brew.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Jamie - episode 2</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/journal/2020/05/25/jamie-episode-2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Jamie - episode 2" /><published>2020-05-25T09:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-05-25T09:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/journal/2020/05/25/jamie-episode-2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/journal/2020/05/25/jamie-episode-2.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;what did you do today?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Went for a walk to the park early morning and bumped into my year 7 maths teacher and her dog. Had a nice chat, then came back to speak to a friend on Zoom, before having two bacon and egg bagels for lunch. Then went for a long walk in the forest, bought some haribo and a pot noodle as a throwback to being a 12 year old kid, ate them outside in the garden, followed by a hot bath.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did you think about something or someone you hadn’t in a while?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Everything I used to do as a kid on summer holidays around this area - including my paper round and the man who ran it. He looked (looks?) suspiciously like Fagin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did you have a meaningful interaction with someone?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
My old maths teacher - was sad to hear that unfortunately she’s got cancer, but is still running (which is her favourite sport) and was great to see how excited she was to see what I was up to now. Also funny she didn’t recognise me at all despite the fact I probably haven’t grown since then either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did anything interesting happen?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Got sent these journal prompts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did you learn something new about yourself?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I love fresh turmeric - gives me loads of energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do you feel about lockdown today?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I felt good. It’s been quite chilled compared to normal London life, but would like to see friends properly!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Additional comments&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Found out the Bourne Stores don’t sell Refreshers any more. This thoroughly disappointed my inner child.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jamie</name></author><summary type="html">what did you do today? Went for a walk to the park early morning and bumped into my year 7 maths teacher and her dog. Had a nice chat, then came back to speak to a friend on Zoom, before having two bacon and egg bagels for lunch. Then went for a long walk in the forest, bought some haribo and a pot noodle as a throwback to being a 12 year old kid, ate them outside in the garden, followed by a hot bath.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/jamie-lockdown.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/jamie-lockdown.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Go for a looooong walk</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/life/2020/05/20/walk.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Go for a looooong walk" /><published>2020-05-20T09:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-05-20T09:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/life/2020/05/20/walk</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/life/2020/05/20/walk.html">&lt;p&gt;as enjoyable as going for a long walk is, I must admit, I can sometimes be quite resistant to the idea of moving (typical. I am so lazy). It’s mostly my inner bitch talking whenever I’m feeling like this. But once you’re doing it, it can be really nice and even feel meditative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think what’s really interesting about this whole pandemic situation (I think I managed to avoid using the word pandemic up until this point!) is that we now really appreciate the ability to go out and be free to move. And one thing that I’ve found useful whenever I’m feeling a little down, or stressed out, is just to go for a little wander. Though again, this is always tricky because whenever I’m feeling like that I almost always instantly just want to curl up into a little ball and just do nothing - even though I know that every time I manage to get my ass out the door I always feel better. It’s quite helpful to leave whatever stressful situation you’re in and have a bit of fresh air.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I went for a little wander yesterday, in search for this monument that commemorates the guy who translated the Bible from Greek into English. I think you’d normally be able to go up to the top but obviously because social distancing is in place, we weren’t able to do that. It was situated on top of this hill, at the Cotswold edge, and the view was absolutely spectacular. You can see Wales from the top of this hill, which is quite something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It kind of makes you think about how small you are - in a good way. I think these are the things that help you put stuff into perspective. This was the extent of my pondering/reflecting though, because apparently I get quite grumpy when I’m hungry &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; cold, so after about 5-10 minutes of ooh-ing and aah-ing, and some pictures, we turned around and headed back (to the kitchen).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of your daily exercise, why not go for a long walk and just…….take in the view, wherever you are. Maybe even leave that rectangle electronic thing behind. You know what I’m talking about, the one that lights up when you touch and tap 😉&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have fun!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jess</name></author><summary type="html">as enjoyable as going for a long walk is, I must admit, I can sometimes be quite resistant to the idea of moving (typical. I am so lazy). It’s mostly my inner bitch talking whenever I’m feeling like this. But once you’re doing it, it can be really nice and even feel meditative.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/walk.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/walk.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Jess - episode 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/journal/2020/05/19/jess-journal-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Jess - episode 1" /><published>2020-05-19T09:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-05-19T09:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/journal/2020/05/19/jess-journal-1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/journal/2020/05/19/jess-journal-1.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;what did you do today?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Today is a work day. I’ve been brought back from furlough, and we’re now doing 4 days a week. It’s been nice so far, we have a mix of busy days and not-so-busy days. I’d say it’s a good balance. There’s been lots of staring at the screen today, and preparing for a presentation. Also tried to do a bit of writing and journalling (to officially launch this lockdown journal project!).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Artist’s Way arrived. If you’re not sure what that is, check out my latest newsletter here. As the geek and weirdo that I am, I got super excited by the smell of the book and the feel of the paper (told you, weird). But most importantly, can’t wait to start reading the book and be like Elizabeth Gilbert. Maybe I’ll  be inspired enough to write a book after I finish reading this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did you think about something or someone you hadn’t in a while?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I thought about my parents (not that I hadn’t thought about them in a while! Promise I do think about them hehehe) The theme of this morning’s meeting was on happiness and who’s made you happy during quarantine. I thought about my parents and the videos they’ve been sending - of my dad shaving his head. Cute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did you have a meaningful interaction with someone (or was it just meaningless zoom faff)?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
A great quiz planning session. Excited about hosting the quiz on Thursday, but not going to lie, these quizzes are relentless. Also made a thank you card that put a smile on the recipient’s face (I think? I hope it wasn’t a fake or forced smile 😛).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did anything interesting happen?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The Artist’s Way arrived! I know I’ve mentioned it in one of the questions, but it just looks so fresh and shiny (and the pages smell so good, I can’t help it).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did you learn something new about yourself?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
That I am a freak. Why do I love smelling books so much?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do you feel about lockdown today?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Okay I think. I’m not sure, really. Had a conversation about what my plans are for the coming month. It’s May already, and I can’t really predict what’s going to happen. It has made me realise how resilient we are as a species because now lockdown kind of feels like the new normal, which is why I’m having trouble imagining what life after lockdown is going to be like. But at the same time, it also makes you think that based on how (relatively) quickly we adjusted to this situation, it’s very likely that we might also readjust fairly quickly to life post-lockdown, and move on and perhaps even forget about everything that we learned during this lockdown?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Additional comments?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I made honey/water ice cubes today. Not sure if it’s going to work, will report back.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jess</name></author><summary type="html">what did you do today? Today is a work day. I’ve been brought back from furlough, and we’re now doing 4 days a week. It’s been nice so far, we have a mix of busy days and not-so-busy days. I’d say it’s a good balance. There’s been lots of staring at the screen today, and preparing for a presentation. Also tried to do a bit of writing and journalling (to officially launch this lockdown journal project!).</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/jess-journal-1.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/jess-journal-1.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Make a Lentil Curry</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/food/2020/05/15/lentil-curry.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Make a Lentil Curry" /><published>2020-05-15T09:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-05-15T09:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/food/2020/05/15/lentil-curry</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/food/2020/05/15/lentil-curry.html">&lt;p&gt;so like I mentioned in the previous post, I’ve been trying to experiment a little bit in the kitchen. Something about being stuck at home I believe.. makes you explore every inch and corner of your house and discover new ways to stay busy and entertained.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other night, having just come back from a run (how cool is it that I can say this now?! I feel like I’ve levelled up or something), naturally I was starving. The original plan was to make this quick lemon pepper chicken recipe - which has been tried and tested. But alas, there was no chicken in the fridge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It did involve some frantic dig down the internet hole to figure out what to cook for dinner. I needed something tasty, something quick, and something which didn’t involve too many complicated ingredients. It was a battle between chickpeas or lentils.. but in the end, lentils won out. Mostly because the recipe I was using had eggs in it, and that we didn’t have enough chickpeas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I based it on this &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.olivemagazine.com/recipes/vegetarian/spiced-crispy-egg-and-lentil-curry/&quot;&gt;recipe&lt;/a&gt;. It ticked all the boxes, except for the ‘quick’ one. Definitely wasn’t the quickest to make - it took 30 minutes just to let the curry simmer. I’d say it took about an hour total - but it was so worth it. Very tasty, and not a lot of complicated ingredients involved!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s what you need:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Curry:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;red lentils 100g&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;onions 2, roughly chopped&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;chopped tomatoes 400g tin&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ground turmeric 1 tsp&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;oil 2 tbsp, for frying&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ground cumin 1 ½ tsp&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ground coriander 1 ½ tsp&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;cardamom pods 4, squashed&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;root ginger a thumb-sized piece, finely chopped&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;garlic 4 cloves, crushed&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;green chillies 2-3, sliced&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;baby spinach 100g, chopped&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;garam masala 1 tsp&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;coriander a small bunch, chopped&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;steamed basmati rice or chapatis to serve&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the crispy eggs you’ll need:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;eggs 6&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ground turmeric ¼ tsp&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;paprika ¼ tsp&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s how to do it:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Put the lentils, onions and tomatoes in a pan with the turmeric and 1 tsp salt. Add water to just cover, then simmer gently for 20 minutes until the lentils are tender&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Drop the eggs into boiling water, cook for 7 minutes then plunge into iced water and leave until cooled.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Heat half the oil in a pan then stir in the cumin, coriander and cardamom. Cook for 2 minutes then stir in the ginger, garlic and chillies. Cook for a few minutes then add the lentil mixture and 100ml water. Cover and simmer for 30 minutes. Add the spinach and cook for another 10 minutes.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Peel the eggs and heat the remaining oil in a frying pan. Add the eggs, turmeric and paprika, then season with salt and cook until the skin starts to blister and crisp up.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Stir the garam masala and coriander into the curry and serve with the halved eggs and rice or chapatis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We didn’t have coriander unfortunately, but I think it would have tasted spectacular with coriander.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you’re looking for an easy recipe, have a go at this and let me know how it goes!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good luck 😊&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jess</name></author><summary type="html">so like I mentioned in the previous post, I’ve been trying to experiment a little bit in the kitchen. Something about being stuck at home I believe.. makes you explore every inch and corner of your house and discover new ways to stay busy and entertained.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/lentil-curry.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/lentil-curry.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>